[{"answer": "He had a pass that apparently allowed him to enter the day the Yard that's right behind me.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "The obvious question, I guess following this is, how does the man with his background a couple of gun-related incidents, discharged from the army of a pattern of misconduct, how does he get clearance to enter one of the most secured military bases in America and do what he did?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, I thought the base was very secured.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Now, there are 3,000 people who work at the base, how secure is it would you say?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "I'm told there are armed security guards, armed police that the civilians that worked there are not allowed to carry a gun, is that correct?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yeah, there are security guards inside the building, outside the buildings, around the building as you enter the gate.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Are you aware of their presence?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know how he was able to get in on the base.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "But he was carrying an AR- 15 assault rifle, another rifle and a handgun, would somebody carrying weapons in the way that he was immediately ring alarm bells inside the base?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "When you come inside the gate, yes, you have to show your cache (ph) card.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Because presumably -- presumably Patricia, you have to go through some kind of security check to get inside the building?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "No, we don't have any metal detectors.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Do you need to go through metal detectors?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "No, I will not.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Are you going back to work Patricia tomorrow?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "I'm terrified.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "What is your feeling towards the man that put you through this and so many of your colleagues?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "That picture really is just emerging Piers.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "On the one hand, he seems quite shy and very well-behaved, never caused any trouble, on the other, a little clue here and there incidents involving firearms, misconduct later being discharged from the Navy, who is the real Aaron Alexis?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "How could somebody like this with this background just walk on to a base, on to the tip like this, and get inside and be in a position to kill all these people?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, I'm a doctor.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Tell me, what prompted you to react like that and expand on what you were saying?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Sure, I'd be happy to tell you.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "How many of you been treating the way you are and what is the current set of their condition?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "I don't know that you can make the determination right now.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Shawn Henry, in terms of the investigation and from all that you gleaned to date, are we dealing, do you think definitely with a long shooter here?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I think that that's actually the right protocol.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "It did some sort of old state of affairs that the FBI seeking information after the shooter is dead, what do you make of that?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "ENRY: Well, I don't know that it's clear right now how he actually got the weapons on to the base whether he was in some type of the work track; I'm not clear on what his access was.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "And are you even more surprised as I am that he's able to walk fully armed into a base of his nature and do what he did?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Well look at DC, first of all in DC you're not allowed to own any semiautomatic rifle.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "How on earth do you justify that tweet?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Well, we don't know where he bought it.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Where did he buy the M-15?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Because I'm telling a fact Ben.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Do you know that he bought it?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, there is a problem here, Piers, when our failure as a nation is to even talk about the complexity of the problem.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Why do you think that's not a problem here?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "On this case.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "I'm saying multiple people have said that they're wrong in terms of their numbers.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "You are saying they are inventing those statistics?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "OTT: No, I didn't say they didn't happen.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Is that what your opposition?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Of those, 30 have happened since 2006.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Is there -- Is it really necessary?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "You can -- Professor Fox at Northeastern University, others have looked at this and they would warn you to be careful not to use those numbers.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "What does make them wrong John Lott?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "It might be as simple as that.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Can it be as simple as that or are we talking about somebody with an underlying serious mental health issue?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Could that in any way had been partly had trigger for what happened?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "But anger manifested into violence by a gun?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Well, I think the answer is to really takes a look at these cases and see are there common threads in there.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "What's the answer?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Well, here is one thing it was shocking to me and it go back a lot of memories from November 5th 2009.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What is your reaction?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Well, right now, today it appears that there is no hope, but there is hope and there's light at the end of tunnel.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "If you can't even get those kind of things in any kind of sensible gun control legislation what hope is there?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Well, a lot of civilians they purchase one because what you have to look at, Piers is that a lot of times different fractions glorify in AR15 or in automatic rifle.", "docId": "130916pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "It is the preferred mass shooters weapon of choice, and yet I don't see any logical reason and you're a military man why any civilian needs to have one of these killing machines?", "qSentId": 436}]